undercovercommissions.com 2011-12-28

# UndercoverCommissions.com Privacy Policy

PRIVACY POLICY

UndercoverCommissions.com takes the job of guarding your personal information with the utmost seriousness.

We will not give any information about you to others without your express permission. Our network of sites uses forms in which you give us contact information (your name, e-mail address, address, telephone number, etc.) so you can receive information from us or to place orders with us. We use your customer information only when it will be important for us to contact you regarding updates or changes to our programs or products and special offers we think you'll find valuable. We also will send you information related to the topics you signed up about to further help in the education process. 

At all times if you find that you wish to stop receiving communication from us, simply click on UNSUBSCRIBE at the bottom of any newsletter that you are a part of. Understand that from time to time you may end up subscribing to several different specialized newsletters that we offer, so you may still continue to receive messages from us, just through a different newsletter. If you are having issues unsubscribing simply send an e-mail to mattbacak@gmail.com and we will assist you. 

We use information gathered about you from our site statistics (for example your IP address ) to help diagnose problems with our server, and to administer our Web site. We also gather broad demographic information from this data to help us improve our site and make your browsing and purchasing experience more enjoyable. This is not linked to any personally identifiable information, except as necessary to prevent fraud or abuse on our system.

Our sites may contain links to other sites. Unfortunately UndercoverCommissions.com, is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites.

Security

You may opt-out of receiving communications from us and our partners at any time. We have the following options for changing and modifying your customer information.

• You may send an email to mattbacak@gmail.com.  

• You may send mail to Catapult Corporation, 2763 Meadow Church Rd. Ste 207, Duluth, GA 30097

As stated previously in this policy, unless we have given you notice and choice, we will not share your personal information except with a third party to assist us in the processing or securing of your personal information or when we are required by law , in the good-faith belief that such action is necessary in order to conform to the edicts of the law, or we must comply with a legal process served on our web site. We may also need to give out your information if one of our partners requires it, but these situations are rare.

Changes in Our Practices

If we make material changes to our information handling practices or other privacy aspects, we will post those changes on this privacy statement prior to their implementation or notify you directly via email. Minor changes will be immediately effective upon reposting to this privacy policy on our network of Web sites.

If you have any questions about our privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, please contact us at:  mattbacak@gmail.com
